[
    { "answer": "a", "question": "あ" },
    { "answer": "i", "question": "い" },
    { "answer": "u", "question": "う" },
    { "answer": "e", "question": "え" },
    { "answer": "o", "question": "お" },
    { "answer": "ka", "question": "か" },
    { "answer": "ki", "question": "き" },
    { "answer": "ku", "question": "く" },
    { "answer": "ke", "question": "け" },
    { "answer": "ko", "question": "こ" },
    { "answer": "sa", "question": "さ" },
    { "answer": "shi", "question": "し" },
    { "answer": "su", "question": "す" },
    { "answer": "se", "question": "せ" },
    { "answer": "so", "question": "そ" },
    { "answer": "ta", "question": "た" },
    { "answer": "chi", "question": "ち" },
    { "answer": "tsu", "question": "つ" },
    { "answer": "te", "question": "て" },
    { "answer": "to", "question": "と" },
    { "answer": "na", "question": "な" },
    { "answer": "ni", "question": "に" },
    { "answer": "nu", "question": "ぬ" },
    { "answer": "ne", "question": "ね" },
    { "answer": "no", "question": "の" },
    { "answer": "ha", "question": "は" },
    { "answer": "hi", "question": "ひ" },
    { "answer": "fu", "question": "ふ" },
    { "answer": "he", "question": "へ" },
    { "answer": "ho", "question": "ほ" },
    { "answer": "ma", "question": "ま" },
    { "answer": "mi", "question": "み" },
    { "answer": "mu", "question": "む" },
    { "answer": "me", "question": "め" },
    { "answer": "mo", "question": "も" },
    { "answer": "ya", "question": "や" },
    { "answer": "yu", "question": "ゆ" },
    { "answer": "yo", "question": "よ" },
    { "answer": "ra", "question": "ら" },
    { "answer": "ri", "question": "り" },
    { "answer": "ru", "question": "る" },
    { "answer": "re", "question": "れ" },
    { "answer": "ro", "question": "ろ" },
    { "answer": "wa", "question": "わ" },
    { "answer": "wo", "question": "を" },
    { "answer": "n", "question": "ん" }
]
